urbamine.de 2019-02-11

# UMS GmbH - Privacy Statement

#### Our contact details

**UMS Urban Mining Solutions GmbH**  
Karlstraße 8 b  
D-42897 Remscheid  
Germany

Fon: +49 2191 4222264  
Fax: +49 2191 4222266

Email: [info@urbamine.de](mailto:info@urbamine.de)

### Privacy statement

As a user of our website, this privacy policy will provide you with all necessary information on how, to what extent and for what purpose we or third parties collect and use data from you. The collection and use of your data is strictly in accordance with the provisions of the Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG) and the German Telemedia Act (TMG). We are particularly committed to the confidentiality of your personal information and therefore work strictly within the limits set by law. The collection of these personal data takes place on a voluntary basis, if it is possible for us. Also, we only pass on this data to third parties with your express consent. We ensure high security for particularly confidential data such as payment transactions or for your requests to us by using SSL encryption. However, we do not want to miss the opportunity to point out the general risks of internet usage over which we have no influence. Especially in email traffic your data is not safe without further precautions and may be captured by third parties.

### Information, cancellation, blocking

At any time you will receive free information about the personal data we have stored about you as well as the origin, the recipient and the purpose of data collection and data processing. In addition, you have the right to request the correction, blocking or deletion of your data. This does not apply to data that is stored as part of to legal regulations or required for the proper conduct of business. To ensure that data can be blocked at any time, data is held in a lock file for control purposes. If data is not recorded by a legal archiving obligation, we delete your data upon your request. Greift die archiving, sperren wir Ihre Data. For all questions and concerns regarding the correction, blocking or deletion of personal data, please contact our data protection officer using the contact data in this privacy policy or at the address stated in the imprint.

### Cookies

We use cookies on our website. These small text files are stored on your PC by our server. They support the presentation of our website and help you navigate our website.  
Cookies collect data about your IP address, browser, operating system and internet connection. We do not associate this information with personal data and do not share it with third parties. In no case are cookies used by us to deliver malicious programs or spyware to your computer.

You may also navigate our website without the use of cookies, but this may result in limited representation and functionality of our offer. If you want to deactivate the cookies, you can do this through special settings in your browser. Please use its help function to make the appropriate changes.

You can manage online ad cookies via the following links:

  * http://www.aboutads.info/choices for the USA
  * http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices for Europe

### Collection of access data

The delivery and presentation of content via our website technically requires the collection of certain data. With your access to our website these so-called server log files are recorded by us or the provider of the web space. These log files do not allow any conclusion about you or your personal details.

The corresponding information consists of the name of the website, the file, the current date, the amount of data, the web browser and its version, the operating system used, the domain name of your internet provider, the referrer URL as the page from which you switched to our site, and the corresponding IP address.

We use this data for the presentation and delivery of our content as well as for statistical purposes. The information supports the provision and constant improvement of our offer. We also reserve the right to retrospectively check the data mentioned, should the suspicion of an illegal use of our offer arise.

### Personal data

In the context of data avoidance and data minimization, we collect personal data only to the extent and for as long as it is necessary for the use of our website or required by law. We take the protection of your personal data seriously and adhere strictly to the relevant legal provisions and to this privacy policy when collecting and processing personal data. If the purpose of the data collection falls away or the end of the statutory storage period is reached, the collected data will be blocked or deleted.

Generally, our website can be used without the transfer of personal data. When we collect personal information (such as your name, address or email address), this data collection is voluntary. Without your explicit consent, this information will not be disclosed to third parties.  
Please note that data on the internet generally cannot always be transmitted securely. Particularly in email traffic, protection during data exchange can not be guaranteed.

### Server Logfiles

The server log files are anonymized data that are collected when you access our website. This information does not allow any conclusions to be drawn personally, but for technical reasons, it is indispensable for the delivery and presentation of our content. Furthermore, they serve our statistics and the constant optimization of our content. Typical log files contain the date and time of access, the amount of data, the browser used for accessing and its version, the operating system used, the domain name of the provider you request, the page from which you came (Referrer URL) to our offer and your IP address. Log files also allow for accurate examination in case of suspected illegal use of our website.

### SSL encryption

Our website uses SSL encryption when it comes to the transmission of confidential or personal content of our users. This encryption is activated, for example, for the processing of payment transactions and requests that you make to us through our website. Please make sure that the SSL encryption is enabled on your side when performing activities. The use of encryption is easy to recognize: The display in your browser bar changes from "http://" to "https://". SSL encrypted data cannot be read by third parties. Submit your confidential information only with activated SSL encryption and contact us in case of doubt.

### Use of Google Analytics

We use the web analytics service Google Analytics from Google Inc. on our website. It uses cookies. These are text files that are stored on your PC and allow analysis of your user behaviour in connection with our website. The cookies generate information that is transmitted to a Google server. These servers are typically located in the United States, but they are Bound to agreements to use the European Economic Area and truncate your IP address before it is sent to the United States. Only in exceptional cases will the IP address be truncated after transmission to the USA. Google evaluates the information provided and provides in this context, other services for us website operators. The determined IP address is not merged with other Google services.

By changing your browser settings, you can prevent the storage of cookies on your computer. However, this may cause display and functional restrictions when using our website.

A browser plugin also prevents the collection and use of the data generated by the cookies. You can download it at the following link: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de  
Learn more about the privacy policies of Google and Google Analytics at:  
http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/de.html or under https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/.

### Google Maps Plugin

We use a plugin of the internet service Google Maps on our website. Google Maps is operated by Google Inc., located in the US, CA 94043, 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View.

By using Google Maps on our website, information about the use of this website and your IP address will be transmitted to and stored on a Google server in the United States. We have no knowledge of the exact content of the submitted data, nor about their use by Google. The company denies in this context the connection of the data with information from other Google services and the collection of personal data. However, Google may transmit the information to third parties.

If you disable Javascript in your browser, you prevent the execution of Google Maps. But then you cannot use any map display on our website.

By using our website, you consent to the described collection and processing of the information by Google Inc..  
Learn more about the privacy policy and terms of service for Google Maps here:  
https://www.google.com/intl/de_de/help/terms_maps.html.

### Google+ Plugin

We use Google+ features on our website. The social network is offered by Google Inc., which is based in the US, CA 94043, 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View.

Google+ allows you to publish content globally using its button. You will also be offered personalized content from Google and partner providers. Google stores your rating (+1) about content and information from websites for which you have clicked on +1.

Your +1 rating can be viewed with your profile name and photo in other Google services. Google collects all your +1 activities. This collection is designed to optimize and personalize the Google offering for you. To use the Google+ platform, create a globally visible profile under a name you choose. The chosen name also applies to the other Google services. If you know your email address, you will be able to access your Google+ profile.

Google uses the data collected in its privacy policy, among other things to compile statistics that are summarized or shared with partner companies. Details on the use of the data and the privacy policy can be viewed at http://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy/ . Under the link you will also find instructions for personal privacy settings on Google+.

### Twitter Plugin

We also use functions of the microblogging service Twitter on our website. The operator of Twitter is Twitter Inc. The US company is based in the US, San Francisco, CA 94103, 1355 Market St, Suite 900.

Main function of Twitter is the "Tweet function". If you use these via our website, you will be linked to your Twitter account. Data exchange with other users and data transfer to Twitter are possible. We are not aware of the content of the data sent to Twitter, nor are we informed about its use. Find out about these questions below http://twitter.com/privacy. There you will find the detailed privacy policy of Twitter. Furthermore, the platform offers you the opportunity to adjust your own privacy settings via http://twitter.com/account/settings .

### XING Plugin

On our website, we use features of XING, a network that particularly wants to promote professional contacts of its members. Provider of this network is the XING AG. It is located in the Dammtorstraße 29-32 in 20354 Hamburg.

If one of our pages with XING features is accessed, it will connect to XING servers. We are not aware that XING stores personal information. To the best of our knowledge XING does not evaluate IP addresses and does not store them.

If you would like more information about XING privacy, you can access the XING privacy policy with the link: https://www.xing.com/app/share?op=data_protection . There you will also learn more about the XING share button.

This privacy statement was created by [www.datenschutzexperte.de](https://www.datenschutzexperte.de/)
